Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Art and Art History, Records SC1101
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Art and Art History, records
1962-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Department of Art and Art History
SC1101
27.25 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
Meeting minutes, photographs and posters documenting the Department of Art and Art History.
Access to Collection
Emeriti files in Series 3 & Accession ARCH-2017-010 are Restricted for 75 years from date of creation. Otherwise, the materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of departmental meeting minutes, photographs and posters documenting the Department of Art and Art History.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Administrative transfer, 2012 & 2016.
Arrangement
The records are arranged in four series: Series 1. Administrative Records; Series 2. Photographs; Series 3. Emeriti files; Series 4. Posters.
Posters.; Photoprints.; Art Exhibits, Student; Art Exhibits; Art--Study and teaching.; Architecture--Study and teaching.; Diebenkorn, Richard; Stanford University. Department of Art and Art History; Elsen, Albert Edward; Diebenkorn, Richard; Stanford University. Department of Art and Art History; Eitner, Lorenz.; Elsen, Albert Edward; Corn, Wanda M.; Oliveira, Nathan; Oliveira, Nathan; Corn, Wanda M.; Stanford University. Department of Art and Art History
- Administrative Records, Series 1
  - Studio Faculty Committee, 1974 Sep-1978 Jun (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Studio Faculty Committee, 1970-1974 Apr (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Art History Faculty Committee, 1989/1990-1994/1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Art History Faculty Meetings, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Art History Faculty Committee, 1978 Sep-1980 Jun (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Art History Faculty Committee, 1976 Sep-1978 Jun (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Art History Faculty Committee, 1974 Sep-1976 Jun (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Art History Faculty Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Studio Faculty Committee, 1978 Sep-1989 Feb (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Art Building: Dedication (includes photographs), 1969 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2006-2007; 14 computer file(s)
- Emeriti files, Series 3 (Accession ARCH.2015-133)
  Access
  Restricted 75 years from date of creation.
  - Corn, Wanda M. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Corn, Wanda M. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gough, Maria (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gough, Maria (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hannah, David G. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Kahn, Matthew S. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kahn, Matthew S. - Promotion to full professor (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kahn, Matthew S. - Promotion to associate professor (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Kahn, Matthew S. - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Kahn, Matthew S. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Martinez, Ruiz B. - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Martinez, Ruiz B. - Promotion and appointment to professor with tenure (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Martinez, Ruiz B. - Reappointment (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Martinez, Ruiz B. - Initial appointment (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Photographs, Series 2
  - Art Building
    - Construction (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Drawing Studio (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Design Studio (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Front Entrance (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Painting Studio (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Lithography Shop (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Interior Class Rooms (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Interior Studios (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Front View (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Sculptures (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Negatives (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Annenburg Auditorium (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Art Library (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Front Area ("The Well") (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Exterior Views (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Front Lobby (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Interior Library (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Interior Slide Library (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Henry Moore (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Photography Lab (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Poncet (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Rare Book Room (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Rosati (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Pomodoro (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Slide Library (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Art Department
    - Visiting Artists Art Historians (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Artist Visitors, circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Visiting Artists (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Art History Programs (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Gallery Artists, circa 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Celebrations (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Staff (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1962-1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Christmas Party, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Graduation (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Students (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Faculty (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Events, Lectures (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Students (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Celebrations Parties, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Gallery Re-opening (photographs by Emily Yates Doerr), 2001 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Artists/Art Openings (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Art Department Museum Publicity (clippings) (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Graduation Ceremony (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Gallery Exhibitions
    - Exhibitions - Museum and Gallery (posters and announcements), 1960s (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - An Exhibition of Far Eastern Sculpture (program), 1953 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Paintings (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Five More Artists - MFA Show, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Paintings Installations (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Folk Art from Three Cultures, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Mendelowitz Watercolors, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Painting in Mid-Century, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Rococo Art, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Paintings by Mark Tobey, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Lithographs by Frank Lobdell, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Photographs from Imogen Cunningham, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Contemporary Graphics, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Diebenkorn at Stanford, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Drawings by Keith Boyle, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Drawings Watercolors by John Altoon, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Aktual Art, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Treasures from Mrs. Stanford's Basement, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Graduate Student Show, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - African Sculpture, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - MFA Show Installation, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Posters, 1973-2014; Series 4
  - Art History
    - Art, Equity and Inequity, 2014-05-08 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents note
      40305
    - African-Americans in Soviet Socialist Realism, 2014-04-10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      40277
    - Lecture Series by Ide Seinosuke: 2/27, 3/13, 3/17, 2014-02-27-2014-03-17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      40237
    - Their Satanic Majesties' Movies: The Rolling Stones in Cinema, 2014-10-30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      40115
    - the Material Imagination, sound, spae, and human cosciousness workshop serires (various dates), 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      2013-2014
    - The Non-Object and Its Vicissitudes in Late-Twentieth Century Brazilian Art, 2013-05-16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      39948
    - The Invisible Acropolis: Was Classical art Meant to be Seen?, 2013-04-11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      39913
    - Death at Work: Barthes and Warhol Look at the Human Face, 2012-11-08 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      39759
    - Corrective Lenses: On the politics of Revision, 2012-10-27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      39747
    - Ends of the Earth: Art of the and to 1974, 2011-12-01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      39416
    - Architecture Drafted; Design Expertise and the World War II Experience, 2012-02-02 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      39479
    - The Artists' Congress: Toward the Birth of a New Imaginary and Image of Africa, 2012-04-12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      39549
    - Idolatry: Nietzsche, Blake, Poussin, 2011-04-20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      39191
    - Volmar, Hildegard, and History: The Case of St. Mattias, 2011-04-14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      39185
    - Volcanic Tourism: Naples, Vesuvius and antiquity, 1730 - 1850, 2011-04-14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Re-staging the Spectacular: Digital Displays Inside and Outside the Home, 2011-04-06 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      39177
    - Unscripted: Xu Bing on Contemporary Currents in Chinese Art, 2011-01-27 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      39108
    - The Invention of African Art, 2011-01-20 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      39101
    - Monumental Snapshots of a Soviet Future, 2011-02-24 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      39136
    - Ends of the Earth: Land Art to 1977 (a work in progress), 2010-11-04 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      39024
    - Abstraction and Naturalism in Byzantine Art, 2010-11-01 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      39021
    - 194X: American Architecture and Abstraction at Mid-Century, 2010-05-21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      38857
    - The Fracturing of Globalisation, 2010-04-12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      38818
    - Picasso, Africa, and Pornography: Les Demoiselles d'Avignon Reconsidered, 2010-04-08 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      38814
    - The Inside Image Out, Japan, 2010-01-28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      38744
    - A Great American Thing: A Symposium in Honor of Wanda Corn, 2009-11-13-2009-11-14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      11/13/09 - 11/14/09
    - Olympian Art: (Inter)national Proposals for Munich '72, 2009-10-15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      38639
    - The Cathedral of Cinema: Fritz Lang's Metropolis, 2009-05-22 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      38493
    - Rising Tide Conference, 2009-04-06-2009-04-30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      04/06 - 30/09
    - The Trouble with Images: Aniconism, Iconoclasm, and the Representation of Islam, 2009-04-16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      38457
    - Pagans in the Church: Raphael's "School of Athens" and Renaissance Cross-Cultural Dialogue, 2009-02-23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      38405
    - Screening the Female Face, 2009-02-12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      38394
    - Conceptual Representation, 2009-01-13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      38364
    - Urbanism and Violence in Grand Ducal Florence, 2008-11-13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      38303
    - Entropy as Monument, 2008-10-23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      38282
    - Installing Time, 2008-05-29 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      38135
    - Urban forms of the Network Society, 2008-05-23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      38129
    - What's Research in Art History Anyway?, 2008-05-08 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      38114
    - Andrea Mategna c. 1460: Imitation and the Force of Images, 2008-04-17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      38093
    - Big Structure, 2008-03-13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      38058
    - Mexican Muralism and the Philanthropic Ogre, 2008-02-14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      38030
    - A Brief History of Time at Cahiers du Cinema, 2007-10-18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      37911
    - Absence as Memory, 2013-11-14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      40130
    - The Encyclopedic Museum in the Post-Colonial Present, 2012-10-18 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      39738
    - Art History Lecture Series Full-year poster of lectures, 2007 - 2008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      2007 - 2008
    - After the World Trade Center and Katrina: Rethinking the City for Our Time, 2006-03-02 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      37316
    - Hollywood Beyond Idelogy, 2011-10-17 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      39371
    - Some Pages from Michaelangelo's Life, with Reflections on Some Other Lives, 2011-05-19 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      39220
    - Italian Cinema 1977-1978: Fantasies of Pastoral Education, 2010-05-06 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      38842
    - Anri Sala's "Long Sorrow", 2009-04-30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      38471
    - Dovzhenko's Revolution and Civil War, 2007-05-16-2007-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      37757
    - Diagnosing Pictures and the Science of Seing in America circa 1900, 2007-05-10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      37750
    - Dance Macabre: On the Ontology of the Marionette, 2006-10-05 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      37533
    - Hesse in Relief, 2007-02-08 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      37659
    - AHLS year-long lecture overview, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      2006 - 2007
    - Negotiating Art's Boundaries: John Sloan, Popular Illustration, and the Figure of the Artist, 2006-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      37399
    - The Death of the Surface or the Superficilaity of the Image: On the Sensuality of Vanity in Premodern Time, 2006-05-11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      37386
    - Seeing, Owning, Knowing: Visual Culture and the Natural History in the Eighteenth Century Spanish Empire, 2006-05-09 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      37384
    - Methodological Discomforts - Interpretive Quarrels: Art History Meets the Garment Union in a 1930s Mural, 2006-04-19 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      37364
    - The Second-Best Photograph by Nick Ut or the Problem of Luck in Photography, 2006-04-03 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      37349
    - Co-Producing Cross-border Action: Technologies of Contact, Masculinity, and te Asia-Pacific Border, 2006-02-14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      37300
    - AHLS year-long lecture overview, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      2005 - 2006
  - Film
    - The City of Lost Children, 2006-10-30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      37558
    - Staging a World: Cinema, Civilization, Dance, 2006-11-30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      37589
    - Capote, 2006-1-25 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      37260
    - Camera Politica: Dusan Makavejev, 2006-4-13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      37356
    - The Films of Jay Rosenblatt, 2006-10-19 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      37547
    - After Great Divides: Time and Identity in Chinese Cinema, 2006-2-28 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      37314
    - Snow Cake, 2007-2-14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      37665
    - Urban Trauma and the Metropolitan Imagination, 2005-5-5-2005-5-7 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      5/5/05 - 5/7/05
    - 8 Short Films, 2014-06-12 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      40340
    - Read-Only vs. Read-Write Culture, 2006-05-02 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      37377
    - 6 Documentary Films by Students in FP114: Introduction to Fim Production, 2014-06-06 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      40334
    - The Last Screening, 2014-06-14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      40342
    - 4 Short Co-Directed Films, 2014-03-18 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      40254
    - Perfect Strangers, 2014-02-05 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      40213
    - 8 Short Films, 2013-12-10 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      40156
    - 5 Documentary Films by Students in FP114: Introduction to Fim Production, 2013-12-06 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      40152
    - Seven Thesis Films, 2013-06-15 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      39978
    - Living in Color, 2013-06-13 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      39976
    - 6 Films by Students in FP114: Introduction to Fim Production, 2013-06-07 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      39970
    - Informant, 2013-04-09 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      39911
    - Four Short Film Fest, 2013-03-20 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      39891
    - 4 Films by Students in FP 114: Introduction to Film Production, 2012-12-07 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      39788
    - Not Fade Away, 2012-10-12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      39732
    - 8 Thesis Films, 2012-06-16 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39614
    - 8 Films by First Year Students in the MFA Program in Documentary Film and Video, 2012-06-14 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39612
    - 6 Short Films by Students in FilmProd 114: Introduction to Film and Video Production, 2012-06-08 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39606
    - "Crash" by David Cronenberg - Driven: A Car Culture Film Series, 2012-06-07 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39605
    - "Used Cars" by Robert Zemeckis - Driven: A Car Culture Film Series, 2012-05-03 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39570
    - "Traffic" by M. Hulot - Driven: A Car Culture Film Series, 2012-04-12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Four Short Films, 2012-03-21 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39527
    - "American Graffiti" - Driven: A Car Culture Film Series, 2012-03-07 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39513
    - "Two Lane Blacktop" by Monte Hellman - Driven: A Car Culture Film Series, 2012-02-09 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39486
    - "Armored Car Robber" by Richard Fleischer - Driven: A Car Culture Film Series, 2012-01-09 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39455
    - Eight Short Films, 2011-12-13 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39428
    - Tokyo Waka, 2011-11-17 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39402
    - Bachelor Days are Over, 2011-10-28 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39382
    - Facts and Poetry: Documentary Films and Video Works by Zhong Chen, 2011-10-13 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39367
    - Eight Thesis Films, 2011-06-11 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39243
    - Eight Color Films, 2011-06-10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39242
    - 6 Short Films by Students in FP114: Introduction to Fim Production, 2011-06-03 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39235
    - Howl, 2011-05-03 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39204
    - Four Short Videos, 2011-03-16 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39156
    - Disorder, 2011-01-19 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39100
    - 8 Short Films, 2010-12-07 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39057
    - 6 Short Films by Students in FP114: Introduction to Fim Production, 2010-12-03 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39053
    - Rapt, 2010-10-29 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      39018
    - Medusa's Raft, 201-10-07 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      38996
    - Eight Thesis Films, 2010-06-12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      38879
    - Eight Color Films, 2010-06-11 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      38878
    - 5 Short Films by Students in FP114: Introduction to Fim Production, 2010-06-04 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      38871
    - La Danse, 2010-04-06 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      38812
    - Four Films, 2010-03-18 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      38793
    - 8 Short Films, 2009-12-10 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      38695
    - Zombieland, 2009-11-19 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      38674
    - MFA Documentary Thesis Films, 2009-06-13 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38515
    - Screening Number 3, 2009-06-11 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38513
    - An Animated Discussion with Chris Wedge, 2009-05-20 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38491
    - Winter Documentaries: Four Short Docs in High Def, 2009-03-17 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38488
    - Wild Combination: A Portrait of Arthur Russell, 2009-05-08 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38479
    - The Times of Harvey Milk, 2009-02-28 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38410
    - The Decay of Fiction, 2009-02-20 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38402
    - Documentary 2010 Collection v.1, 2008-12-09 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38329
    - Bi-Cultural Life on the US/Mexico Border, 2008-10-22 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      38281
    - Eight Thesis Films, 2008-06-14 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      38151
    - Eight Color Films, 2008-06-10 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      38147
    - An Evening with Alexander Payne, 2008-06-01 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      38138
    - An Evening of Films with Audrius Stonys, 2008-04-10 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      38086
    - Werner Herzog at Stanford, 2008-02-25-2008-02-26 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      38041
    - On Set with Bertrand Tavernier, 2007-11-14 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      37934
    - Zelimir Zilnik at Stanford, 2007-11-08-2007-11-09 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      37932
    - A Conversation with Jeffrey Katzenberg, 2007-10-11 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      37904
  - Job Talks
    - Turning to the Goddess: Anachronism, Secularity, and the "Late Stye" of Tyeb Mehta and K.G. Subramanyan, 2014-02-11 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      40219
    - From Archive to Gallery, 2014-01-28 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      40205
    - Sensory Ethnography: Documentary Practice at the Intersection of Art, Cinema, and Anthropology, 2014-01-15 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      40192
    - Encounters with the Attention Ethic, 2014-01-13 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      40190
    - Latent Engagements, 2014-01-08 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      40185
    - A Matter of Time, 2013-02-21 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      39864
    - Everything Must Go! Restless Objects and Diverted Production Channels, 2013-02-19 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      39862
    - All Forms of Attraction, 2014-02-04 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      39847
    - Painters and Architects, 2013-01-23 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      39835
    - Impossible Design: Porsenna's Tomb and French Visionary Architecture, 2013-01-14 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      39826
    - Im/Material Bernini, 2014-01-16 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      39828
    - Looking and Listening, 2012-12-05 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      39786
    - Into the Archives!, 2012-11-26 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      39777
    - Alan Michelson's Third Bank of the River: Diplomatic Aesthetics and Globalization, 2012-02-08 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      39485
    - Memory in Fragments: The Lives of Ancient Maya Sculptures, 2012-02-14 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      39491
    - History, Identity, and Justice in Sixteenth-Century Michoacan, Mexico, 2012-02-27 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      39501
    - John Sloan: Figuring the Painter in the Crowd, 2011-05-11 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      39218
    - Quarantined: Alice Austen and the Secret History of American Art, 2011-05-09 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      39210
    - Actual Size: The Compass of Images from Audubon to Johns, 2011-04-19 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      39190
    - The Madness of Art: Georgia O'Keeffe and Virgina Woolf, 2011-04-04 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      39175
    - Computer Architectures: Between Parlor and Coal Cellar, 2010-03-08 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      38783
    - Modern is Baroque: Architecture and Experience circa 1900, 2010-03-04 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      38779
    - Computational Beauty: The Kantian of Contemporary Architecture, 2010-03-01 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      38776
    - Practicing Negressity, 2010-02-17 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      38764
    - Marcus Garvey in Stereograph: James VanDerZee, the UNIA, and the Photographic Practices of Diaspora, 2010-02-09 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      38756
    - Displaying Difference in Adrian Piper's Mythic Being, 2010-02-02 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      38749
    - Fragmentary Views, 2009-01-22 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      38373
    - Conceptual Representation, 2009-01-13 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Dakar after the Revolution: Djibril Diop Mambety's Contras' City and May '68, 2008-05-27 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      38133
    - The Whole Earth as a Public Sphere: design discourse and scological politics in the long 1970s, 2003-05-23 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Art, Technoloy, and Illusion: de Loutherbourg's Eidophusikon, 2008-05-19 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      38125
    - The Sculpting of Piet Mondrian's Furniture, 2008-05-05 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      38111
    - In Michaelangelo's Mirror: Daniele da Volterra from the 1540's, 2007-03-12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      37691
    - The Poetics of the Archaeological Garden in Renaissance Rome, 2007-03-05 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      37684
    - Ilusion, Imagination, and Prophecy in Raphael's Later Works, 2007-03-01 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      37680
    - Off the Charts the Song-Poem Story, 2007-02-26 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      37677
    - Daven Gee, 2007-02-21 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      37672
    - Adele Horne, 2007-02-12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      37663
  - Art Practice and Gallery
    - Frame by Frame Senior Show, 2014-06-04-2014-06-15 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      6/4/2014 - 6/15/2014
    - Recent Projects: REXOMA, 2007-03-07 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      37686
    - Michele Kong, 2007-03-06 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      37685
      - Won Ju Lim, 2007-03-01 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Web Projects Course promotion poster, 2006 Winter (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Winter 2006
    - Yumi Roth, 2007-02-28 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      37679
    - Camille Utterback & Heike Liss, 2005-05-15 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      38121
    - Digital Sansuhwa, 2008-05-01 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      38107
    - Charming Augustine, 2008-04-24 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      38100
    - From the Archives: Installation ad Performative Works, 2008-02-07 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      38023
    - Terry Berlier, 2008-02-20 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      38036
    - The Living Tissue of Art: About the Tissue Culture & Art Project & the Developmet of an Artistic Research laboratory, 2007-11-15 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      37939
    - Laylah Ali, 2007-11-01 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      37925
    - Stanford Design Program - Master's Presentations, 2009-06-13 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Dan Graham, 2009-02-17 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      38399
    - People and Places: a peripatetic practice, 2009-01-27 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      38378
    - Vik Muniz, 2008-10-15 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      38274
    - Matt Kahn A Legacy of Excellence, 2010-05-28 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      38864
    - Making Waves, 2010-04-15 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      38821
    - Beyond Boundaries, 2010-02-11 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      38758
    - The Cinematic Myth Machine, 2011-05-26 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      39227